[Fragments of Truth]
[Episode 19]
Thank you for coming to see me.
I'm not here to interrogate you.
I'm here as your friend.
I wanted to talk to you.
I've already told your colleagues
everything I know.
Have you ever
seen
or heard anyone
talk about Han Shuang?
Sun Jiahao told me
about your sister's disappearance
so I could get close to you.
I don't know anything else.
Did Sun Jiahao have
any other hideouts or safe houses?
How did you usually contact each other?
We didn't
see each other often.
He always called me.
When you spoke on the phone,
did you hear anything unusual
or anything you may have overlooked?
A few times,
I could faintly hear
a girl crying on the other end.
Then he'd say
that if she didn't obey,
he'd send her to the factory.
The factory?
What kind of factory?
I don't know.
Han Ning.
I'm sorry.
We could have been
good friends.
Who would have thought...
After you finish serving your sentence,
perhaps
we can have a proper drink together.
Where are we?
Where is this place?
No idea.
How did you get here?
Is anyone there?
Didn't Han Ning wake up?
Old He isn't back yet?
He's off enjoying himself.
Hey.
A leader shouldn't gossip
about people behind their backs.
Master.
Captain Ren.
How are you feeling?
Much better.
I request to return to duty.
All right.
Since everyone's back,
I'd like to say a few words.
The Jiang Li murder case
has formally gone to prosecution.
The bureau
has nominated us for a commendation.
The truth can be cruel.
But we all know
no matter the reason,
we can never seek justice
by fighting evil with evil.
In the Sun Jiahao case,
the chain of evidence is complete.
The criminal facts are clear.
Captain Ren.
I believe
there was a third person
at the crime scene.
But I need more evidence
to substantiate that theory.
All right.
Is everyone there?
Uncle He.
Hey.
I collected a DNA sample
from the fetus in Xiao Ting's body.
Guess what I found?
Go on.
I found a match in hospital records:
a paternity test from seven years ago.
Take a look.
This man is the baby's father.
Hello.
Who are you looking for?
We're from Criminal Investigation.
We need to ask Mr. Wang Guosheng
a few questions.
Is he home?
He's home.
That was fast.
Officers,
anything I can do?
Have you been to Night Flight Club?
Night Flight...
That rings a bell.
There was definitely demand
for that kind of business back then.
I went to quite a few nightclubs
and private clubs.
Well...
You should know this man, right?
This is a police inquiry.
Be serious.
All right.
I'll be serious.
I stopped going there years ago.
I've turned over a new leaf.
So the prodigal son returned.
This woman...
Do you know her?
Think carefully before you answer.
She doesn't ring a bell.
Let me refresh your memory.
Her name is Xiao Ting.
She died seven years ago.
Her body was recently found
on Cuiping Mountain.
She was seven months pregnant
when she died.
So?
What does that have to do with me?
I don't even know her.
Seven years ago, you
had a prenatal paternity test done.
She was carrying
your child.
Now I remember.
That doesn't prove
the baby was mine, does it?
She may have been with another man
afterward.
Even after a body has lain dead
for seven years,
we can still collect DNA.
Officers,
I didn't kill anyone.
I swear I didn't kill her.
Her pregnancy was completely unexpected.
I gave her money.
I gave her a lot of money.
I... I just wanted a child.
I could never kill or harm anyone.
You don't even remember
what the mother looked like.
Don't you feel any guilt?
Please come to the station with us.
Back then,
I often took my clients
to Night Flight Club.
Over time, I got to know Brother Hao.
Later,
they kept offering me
'new merchandise.'
By 'new merchandise,' I mean...
That's beside the point.
What I mean is...
One day, their manager came to me.
Brother.
Come outside.
I need to talk to you.
Brother.
Hey.
What is it?
Why are you here at this hour?
Brother, something happened.
That girl from last time is pregnant.
It's most likely yours.
What do you mean, mine?
Did the police tell you?
Did the doctor tell you?
No.
That girl is notoriously stubborn.
Only someone forceful like you
could get your way with her.
She was hurt last time
and hasn't been with anyone else.
Mr. Xu.
What do you mean?
Brother, I didn't mean anything by it.
I only came to let you know.
Do you want to keep it or abort it?
Either way, I'll need some money.
Does
Brother Hao know about this?
Huh?
Brother.
I shouldn't have said that.
Huh?
Fine.
Take it.
Wow, Brother.
This is far too generous.
I can't take this much.
Tomorrow,
find a place
and run a proper test.
If it's mine,
don't worry,
money won't be a problem.
But you have to promise me
you'll keep the baby safe.
But if it's not mine,
then Brother Hao
will owe me an explanation.
Don't worry, Brother.
That won't be a problem.
I'll take care of it for you.
I'm leaving, Brother.
♪I stand in a fire-tempered jungle♪
♪Withered leaves fall
as my strength runs dry♪
♪Dust swirls as I clench my fists♪
♪I strategize, my faith my armor♪
♪My defiance spills onto concrete♪
♪Even thick fog can't hide
my clear gaze♪
♪Let neon turn to thorns♪
♪Flying low as the stars shift and turn♪
♪Escape the maze,
transcend the challenge♪
♪The meter starts, breaking the silence♪
♪A beam cuts through
a crack in the wall♪
♪This rhythm and noise
echo through the streets♪
♪Don't be afraid. No one will answer♪
♪Why is that child crying?♪
♪The shrinking scar on my arm♪
♪Means I've grown up♪
♪You can trust me when I say that♪
♪The wound still aches♪
♪Like a biting winter♪
♪But a spark still glows♪
[Copyright in this complete short drama]
[Jointly owned by Beijing Hualu New
Media Information Technology Co., Ltd.]
[and Youku Information Technology
(Beijing) Co., Ltd.]
[Youku Information Technology (Beijing)
Co., Ltd. ("YOUKU") holds the]
[exclusive worldwide rights to online
distribution and broadcasting.]